sidbi.in 2017-03-26

# Privacy Policy :: Small Industries Development Bank of India

**SIDBI’s Privacy Policy**

**This privacy policy sets out how Small Industries Development Bank of India (SIDBI – the Bank) uses and protects any information that a person who visits the site http://www.sidbi.in/ and provide information to the Bank (the Visitor).**

The Bank endeavors to safeguard and protect the Visitor’s privacy.

The Bank may change this policy from time to time. You may like to check this web page periodically for recent updates.

## Who is covered by this Policy?

All persons who visit the website http://www.sidbi.in and provide information to the Bank online are covered under this Policy. This Policy does not cover the information provided through other modes of communication to the Bank

## What information does the Bank collect?

We may collect information like:

  * Name, contact and other information that the Bank believes is relevant and necessary to conduct the Bank’s business.
  * Demographic information such as preferences, interests, etc.

By providing email address, telephone numbers and other contact information, the Visitor agrees that the Bank may contact him/her by one or more of the modes of communications.

THE BANK WILL NEVER COLLECTS INFORMATION THAT IS PERSONAL AND CONFIDENTIAL IN NATURE LIKE PASSWORDS, ATM PIN, ETC.

## What the Bank does with the gathered information?

The use / purpose for which any information collected from the Visitor, through the website of the Bank, will vary depending upon the circumstances. Broadly, they may comprise all or any one or more of the following purposes (but shall not be restricted to):

  * To use the information for internal record keeping;
  * To use the information to improve our products and services;
  * To use the information for normal business functioning;
  * To send periodically promotional communication about new products, special offers or other information, which the Bank thinks the Visitor, may find interesting;
  * To contact the Visitor periodically for market research purposes. The Bank may contact the Visitor by email/post or by any other suitable mode of communication. We may use the information to customise the website according to the Visitors’ interests.

## Access to the collected information:

  * The access to the information provided through the Bank’s website would only be given to authorised employees or other SIDBI Group Companies or affiliates or authorised agents or service provider for normal business purposes, only on need to know basis.
  * The Bank may be required, from time to time, to disclose the Visitor’s information to Governmental or judicial bodies or Regulators or any person to whom the Bank is under an obligation to make disclosure under the requirements of any law.

## Security

The Bank’s endeavor is to ensure that information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, the Bank has put in place suitable systems and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that it collects online. The Bank may also work with third parties for Web traffic analysis to research certain usage and activities on parts of the Bank’s website. The Web analysis software is used to find out more about the Visitor, including the Visitor demographics, behaviour and usage patterns, for more accurate reporting and to improve the effectiveness of the Banks’ marketing.

## Cookies

The Bank’s website does not use Cookies.

## Links to other websites

The Bank’s website may contain links to other websites of interest. Please note that once the Visitor opts to link to other websites by leaving the Bank’s site, the Bank shall not be responsible for protection of further disclosure of information and this Privacy Policy / statement cease to be applicable for such disclosure of information. The Visitor may therefore, like to exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to those websites.  
**IMPORTANT:** The Bank reserves its right to amend the present Privacy Policy at any time and will place such amended Privacy Policy, if any, on its website. This Privacy Policy is neither intended to and nor does it create any contractual rights whatsoever or any other legal rights, nor does it create any obligations on the Bank in respect of any other party or on behalf of any party. By accessing this website and any of its pages you are agreeing to the terms set out above.

Policy document
